thinkcash.com 2010-05-28

# Online Personal Loans, Fast Cash Loans - ThinkCash

At ThinkCash your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect and how we use that information and is applicable if you have applied for service with ThinkCash, or if you are a current or former customer. This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 1, 2008. 

**PROTECTING THE PRIVACY OF CUSTOMER INFORMATION**

We are committed to protecting your privacy and to implementing technology that gives you the most powerful and secure online experience. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to transmit and store information about you. For instance, we use computer virus protection software, firewalls, and a 128 bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) for data transmission to ensure that your information is secure. We are constantly evaluating new advances in security technology and techniques to provide the best possible protection for information about you. In addition, we permit only authorized employees who have a job-specific purpose and are trained in the proper handling of customer information to have access to your information. 

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU**

We collect "nonpublic personal information" about you from several sources: 

  * Information you provide through on-line forms, registration forms, surveys, and or other entries, such as your name, address, drivers' license number or other government issued photo ID, social security number, email addresses, assets and income;
  * Non-personally identifiable information such as, web page http headers (home server domain names, IP address, type of client computer, and type of Web browser);
  * Information, user specific or aggregate, on what pages our visitor’s access;
  * The e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with us via e-mails;
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others, such as payment history and loan balances; and
  * Information we receive from third parties, such as consumer reporting agencies and other lenders, regarding creditworthiness and credit history.

**HOW WE USE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

The information we collect about you is primarily used to provide services to you and contact you regarding administrative notices. We may also use your information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our agreements with you, including this Privacy Policy. 

We may use your contact information to send you information about our company and promotional material from our partners. We may also use your personal, demographic and profile data to improve our website, for statistical analysis, for marketing and promotional purposes, and for editorial or feedback purposes for our advertisers. Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future e-mails or postal mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and/or status of orders placed online. 

**PARTIES TO WHOM WE DISCLOSE**

We reserve the right to share, rent, sell, or otherwise disclose data we collect to our affiliates, as well as to non-affiliated third parties, including but not limited to magazine publishers, retailers, and direct marketers. Any non-affiliated third party we share, rent, sell, or otherwise disclose data to will be carefully prescreened by us, determined by us to be reputable, and will use the personal data for marketing products and services which we determine, in our sole judgment, that you might find of interest. 

**Information We Share With Affiliates:**

Some of our services are provided using our affiliates, and we share all of the nonpublic personal information that we collect with them in order to fulfill the services you have requested. 

We may also share your non-public personal information with our affiliates, who may offer you a variety of products and services.

**Information We Share With Third Parties:**

We use certain non-affiliated third parties as service providers, and we share all of the nonpublic personal information that we collect with them in order to fulfill the services you have requested. If you are from a jurisdiction the Lender and/or ThinkCash do not service, or if you are declined credit by Lender, leaving the third box of the Terms and Conditions section of the application “checked” means that you request that your application be forwarded by us to other potential lender(s) for evaluation, and to other providers of products & services. You understand this is a service for you to be considered for alternative sources of financing. You further understand another lender may offer credit on different terms and conditions than presented by us. You understand you may or may not be offered credit from an alternate lender and you should review the privacy policy and other terms and conditions of any lender prior to applying for or accepting credit. We do not charge you directly for this service, however, we may receive consideration from other non-affiliated parties.

We may disclose information we collect to _other lenders_ or financial institutions with which we have a marketing and servicing agreement, such as banks and our affiliates.

_We may share your non-public personal information with other non-affiliated third party companies, who may offer you a variety of products and services._

We may also disclose information we collect to non-affiliated third parties as permitted by law.

If you prefer that we not disclose non-public personal information about you to other potential lenders or non-affiliated third parties, you may opt out of those disclosures, that is, you may direct us not to make those disclosures (other than disclosures permitted by law). If you wish to opt out of disclosures to non-affiliated third parties, you may do so as specified in the EXPLANATION OF OPT-OUT RIGHTS section of this policy. 

**Information About Former Customers**

All information sharing referenced herein with respect to how we use or disclose nonpublic personal information shall also apply to former customers.

**CONTACT PREFERENCES**

You can express a preference for receiving telephone and email contacts from ThinkCash. Specifically, we may send you email(s) regarding our service from time to time or call to remind you about upcoming payments. If you do not wish to receive these emails or phone calls, you may (1) go to [ www.thinkcash.com](http://www.thinkcash.com/) and email us, (2) utilize the ‘unsubscribe’ option on emails you may receive from us, or (3) contact [www.thinkcash.com](http://www.thinkcash.com/) Customer Service at (866) 614-7099 to change your contact preferences. By electing to opt-out of receiving contacts by telephone, mail, or email, you will not receive updates on new product information or special offers. 

Notwithstanding the above, we may send out periodic emails informing you of technical service issues related to a service you requested. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe from these mailings as they are considered an essential part of the service you have requested. 

In addition, we reserve the right to contact you regarding your account status and changes to subscriber agreements, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to you and/or your loan. 

**ACCURACY OF YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION**

We have established procedures to ensure that your financial information is accurate, current and complete, in keeping with reasonable industry standards. We continually strive to maintain complete and accurate information about you and your accounts. Should you ever believe that our records contain inaccurate or incomplete information about you, please notify us. We will investigate your concerns and correct any information we determine to be inaccurate.

You may change your information on your application online by logging into the website and selecting "Update Info."

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Because circumstances and technologies change, we reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying you of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy or by posting the changes online at our website.

**ADDITIONAL SECURITY PRECAUTIONS**

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your login information ; do not share this with others. If you use this site you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account, password, and restricting access to your computer. You agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account and password.

**"COOKIE" POLICY**

To ensure we are publishing content customers need and want [www.thinkcash.com ](http://www.thinkcash.com/)collects user specific and aggregated site visitation statistics using cookies. When someone visits the web site, a cookie is placed on the customer's machine (if the customer accepts cookies). If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the [www.thinkcash.com ](http://www.thinkcash.com/) web site, you will not be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the site. 

**EXPLANATION OF OPT-OUT RIGHTS  
NOTICE TO VERMONT, NORTH DAKOTA, AND CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS **

We will not disclose information about you with affiliates or non-affiliated, third party companies or financial institutions, other than as required or permitted by law, without your express permission.

**NOTICE TO RESIDENTS IN ALL OTHER STATES**

If you wish to opt out of disclosures to affiliates and non-affiliated third parties (including other potential lenders) prior to the sharing of any information, you may “un-check” the third box of the Terms and Conditions section on our application. 

If you wish to “opt-out” of disclosure of information with affiliates and non-affiliated third party companies or financial institutions performing marketing services on our behalf or with whom we have joint marketing agreements (other than as allowed by law) at any time after application, log into your account, go to the Change Account Preferences page and state your information sharing and contact preferences. 

By electing to opt-out of information sharing you will not receive updates on new products, services, or special offers. We may still send out periodic emails informing you of technical service issues related to a service you requested. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe from these mailings as they are considered an essential part of the service you have requested.

**NOTICE TO NEVADA RESIDENTS REGARDING CORPORATE DO-NOT-CALL REGISTRIES**

Pursuant to Nevada state law, if you would like more information regarding this notice or Nevada's law regarding corporate do-not-call registries, you can contact us at the toll-free number or address included in this notice below or the Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of the Nevada Attorney General at 555 E. Washington Street, Suite 3900, Las Vegas, Nevada 89101. Phone: (702) 486-3132 / Email: [BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us](mailto:BCPINFO@ag.state.nv.us)

**CHILDREN AND THE INTERNET**

We respect the privacy of your children, and we comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). We do not knowingly collect or retain personally identifiable information from consumers under the age of thirteen (13). You must be at least eighteen (18) years of age to obtain services from us. 

**WHO DO YOU CONTACT WITH QUESTIONS?**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of this web site, please contact us by sending a letter to:

ThinkCash   
Attn: Privacy Officer  
P.O. Box 101842  
Ft. Worth, TX 76185  
or  
(866) 614-7099   
or  
Sending us an e-mail at: [support@thinkcash.com ](mailto:support@thinkcash.com)
